hi folks its Matt again so we've been
嗨，大家好，马特，所以我们一直
looking at Nash equilibrium and
看纳什均衡和
understanding play and in settings where
了解比赛以及在哪些地方进行比赛
we make those kinds of predictions and
我们做出这样的预测，
we've also been looking a little bit at
我们也一直在关注
dominance relationships and and now
主导关系和现在
let's talk about strictly dominated
让我们谈谈严格控制
strategies and iterative removal of
策略和迭代删除
those which is another way to analyze a
那些是分析
game so you know when you when you're
游戏，让您知道何时何地
talking about game theory there's many
谈论博弈论，有很多
different ways that people can think
人们可以思考的不同方式
about analyzing games in terms of
关于分析游戏
stability in terms of predicting what
预测什么方面的稳定性
people are going to do what logic can be
人们将尽其所能
applied and this is another important
应用，这是另一个重要的
way of looking at games and they give us
看游戏的方式，它们给了我们
some insights so the idea of when we
一些见解，这样的想法，当我们
start thinking about rationality in game
开始考虑游戏的合理性
theory that the basic premise here has
这里的基本前提具有的理论
been that players maximize their payoff
玩家获得最大回报
so they're basically trying to maximize
所以他们基本上是试图最大化
their payoffs and again it doesn't
他们的回报，但事实并非如此
necessarily mean that they're just
一定意味着他们只是
greedy payoffs could be that they you
贪婪的回报可能是他们你
know they are altruistic public-minded
知道他们是无私的公众意识
etc but the the premise here is that
等等，但前提是
there's something some objective
有一些目标
function that people have and they tend
人们拥有的功能，他们倾向于
to do things that will give them higher
做一些能让他们更高的事情
payoffs rather than lay out lower
回报而不是低调
payoffs okay so in terms of iteration on
收益还可以，所以就迭代而言
this logic what we're going to be
这种逻辑，我们将成为
thinking about is what if all players
如果所有玩家都在想
know that other players maximize their
知道其他玩家会最大化他们的
payoffs and we have an idea of what the
回报，我们对
structure of the game is then what does
游戏的结构是什么
that mean for the game can can we make
这意味着我们可以制作游戏
deduce something about what should be
推论应该做些什么
played in the game and what if all
玩游戏，如果有的话
players know that all players know that
玩家知道所有玩家都知道
that players are rational in this sense
在这种意义上，玩家是理性的
so you can you know take this what if I
所以你知道吗，如果我
know that you know that I know and and
知道你知道我知道，并且
and so forth you can take this ad
依此类推，您可以投放此广告
absurdum but it's an important concept
荒谬，但这是一个重要的概念
and understanding what it yields gives
并了解它产生了什么
us some insight into games and gives us
我们对游戏有所了解，并为我们提供了
some predictability now you know going
一些可预测性，现在您知道要去
through very very high levels of this
通过非常高的水平
are questionable but nonetheless the
值得怀疑，但是
logic here and the predictions that are
这里的逻辑和预测
made will give us some understanding of
作出将使我们对
games that we can use in analyzing
我们可以用来分析的游戏
equilibrium and doing other things with
平衡和做其他事情
it so you know we can take this logic
所以你知道我们可以采用这种逻辑
fully two of to its full logic
完整逻辑中的两个
conclusion okay so in terms of strictly
结论好吧，所以严格来讲
dominated strategies that means a
主导策略，这意味着
strategy which which is all there's some
这就是全部的策略
other strategy which always does better
总是做得更好的其他策略
than it it can never be a best reply so
比它永远不可能是最好的答复，所以
so we'll make that clear in a second so
所以我们一会儿讲清楚
basically that means that that if this
基本上，这意味着如果这
is a strategy that that never does well
是永远做不到的策略
there's something which does always
有些事情总是
better than this
比这更好
against any strategy of the other
反对对方的任何策略
players then basically it's never going
玩家然后基本上永远不会
to be played so this is essentially a
要播放，所以这本质上是
strategy we can just safely ignore if we
策略，我们可以放心地忽略是否
think players are rational they should
认为球员应该理性
never play a strictly dominated strategy
从不玩严格控制的策略
there's something else which does better
还有其他更好的东西
in all circumstances for them so we
在任何情况下对他们来说，所以我们
remove those from the game and the idea
从游戏和想法中删除那些
of iteration is we take those out now
迭代是我们现在将那些取出
we've got a simpler game now let's do
我们有一个更简单的游戏，让我们开始
the same thing right so there might be
同样的事情，所以可能会有
something which is now strictly
现在严格的东西
dominated in this thing so a player
在这个东西上占主导地位，所以一个球员
should never play this once we get to
一旦到达
this reduced game and then we take those
这个减少的游戏，然后我们拿那些
out and we get an even further reduced
出去，我们得到进一步减少
game and so forth
游戏等等
and we just keep iterating on that it
我们只是不断地迭代它
leaves us with some prediction and then
给我们一些预测，然后
we think that the only thing that's
我们认为唯一的是
logical if there's rational players and
如果有理性的参与者和
they understand that other players are
他们了解其他玩家
rational and so forth they're going to
理性等等，他们将
be left inside that sub game okay so the
留在那个子游戏里面好吧，所以
running this process - its termination
运行此过程-终止
is called the iterated iterated removal
称为迭代迭代删除
of strictly dominated strategies so in
严格控制的策略，所以在
terms of formal notation what are we
形式符号的术语我们是什么
saying here a strategy a sub I for some
在这里说一个策略
player I is strictly dominated by some
玩家我被某些人严格控制
other strategy of the same player a
同一玩家的其他策略
prime I if what's true these the payoff
素数I如果这是真的，那么回报
that the person gets from playing AI the
这个人从玩AI中得到的
one that's strictly dominated is worse
严格控制的情况更糟
strictly lower okay that's important
严格降低，这很重要
that this is a strict inequality then
那是一个严格的不平等
the payoff that they would get by
他们将获得的回报
playing a prime no matter what the other
不管对方玩什么
players do so this is a for all sign for
玩家这样做是为了所有人
every possible strategy of the other
对方的所有可能策略
players no matter what they do this one
玩家不管他们做什么
AI is worse than
人工智能比
payoff for AI prime okay so no there's
AI Prime的回报还可以，所以没有
no circumstance in which you can do as
没有可以做的情况
well it always does strictly worse that
好吧，这总是会变得更糟
means it's a it's a strategy where
意味着这是一项战略，
you're just strictly better off playing
严格来说，你玩得更好
a prime I that's the concept of strict
素我是严格的概念
domination okay so let's have an idea
统治好了，让我们有个主意
now of iterative iterated removal of
现在迭代删除
strictly dominated strategies so here's
严格控制的策略，所以这是
a game a 3x3 game it's got a bunch of
一个3x3游戏，其中有很多
different payoffs in it we look at it we
在不同的回报，我们看着它，我们
begin to think okay let's suppose you
开始想好吧，让我们假设你
want to find the Nash equilibrium with
想找到纳什均衡
this game well it gets a little
这个游戏好一点
complicated because you have to if you
复杂，因为您必须
think about mixed strategies or pure you
考虑混合策略或纯粹的你
have to consider all the possible
必须考虑所有可能
combinations one thing we can begin to
结合我们可以开始的一件事
do is look for strictly dominated
就是寻找严格控制的
strategies and just get rid of those so
策略，并摆脱那些，所以
for instance in this game what's true if
例如在这个游戏中，如果
we look at this game we notice that R is
我们看这个游戏，我们注意到R是
strictly dominated by C right so the the
严格由C权利支配，因此
column player gets a strictly lower
专栏播放器严格降低
payoff in every one of these entries
这些条目中的每一个都有回报
then they get in every one of these
然后他们进入其中的每一个
entries so you would be strictly better
参赛作品，所以您绝对会更好
playing C than R no matter what the
不管玩C比R
other player does whether the other
其他玩家是否
player goes up middle or down Center
玩家在中上或下中上
always does better than R or even if the
总是比R更好，或者即使
other player mixed so whatever the other
其他玩家混在一起，无论其他
player does you get a strictly higher
玩家你得到严格的更高
payoff from the center than R so we
中心的收益比R高，所以我们
should just get rid of our altogether
应该完全摆脱我们
and now we've got a simpler game right
现在我们有了一个更简单的游戏
so the idea is boom we get rid of our
所以想法是繁荣，我们摆脱了
all together now we've got a simpler
现在在一起，我们有了一个更简单的方法
game
游戏
okay so let's iterate on that logic so
好吧，让我们迭代该逻辑，以便
now there's no domination strict
现在没有严格的统治
domination any longer between for the
之间的统治不再
for the column player because the column
对于专栏播放器，因为专栏
player is actually indifferent between
玩家之间实际上无动于衷
left and center of the other player
另一个玩家的左和中
plays middle but one thing we do notice
扮演中间角色，但我们确实注意到一件事
here is that the middle strategy of the
这是
row player is not dominated right so the
行播放器没有被主导，所以
middle strategy does strictly worse than
中间策略确实比
the up strategy for the row player right
排球运动员的正确策略
so three is better than one two is
所以三胜于一二
better than one no matter what happens
不管发生什么都胜过一个
you're better off playing up then middle
你最好先玩然后再中
so M is strictly dominated by you
所以M严格由你主导
in this case we can get rid of em
在这种情况下，我们可以摆脱em
together that collapse the game further
一起使游戏进一步崩溃
so now we're iterating we've got a
所以现在我们要迭代
simpler game now we see that in this
简单的游戏，现在我们看到
case now once we've done this removal
现在，一旦完成删除操作
now C is dominated by L right so the
现在C由L主导，所以
column player would always get better
专栏选手总是会变得更好
playing L in this game then sorry would
在这个游戏中玩L然后对不起
always be better off playing C than L in
总是比在L中玩C更好
this game so this the payoff is always
这个游戏，所以回报永远是
higher playing C than playing L so L is
玩C比玩L高，所以L是
strictly dominated by C we can get rid
严格由C主导，我们可以摆脱
of L simplify the game further you can
的L可以进一步简化游戏
see where this is going
看看这是怎么回事
boom we're down to a very simple game
繁荣，我们只能依靠一个非常简单的游戏
now the if this is the game is left the
现在，如果这是游戏剩下的
role player is better off playing down
角色扮演者最好淡化
and up boom so what do we end up with we
和繁荣，那么我们最终会得到什么
end up with down and center being the
最终落下并居中
only things that are left once we've
一旦我们离开，只有剩下的东西
done this full iteration so we started
完成了整个迭代，所以我们开始了
with a fairly complicated game we end up
有了一个相当复杂的游戏，我们最终
making a very simple prediction that the
做出非常简单的预测
only thing is left after iteratively
迭代之后只剩下一件事
eliminating strictly dominated
消除严格控制
strategies is down for the role player
策略对角色扮演者不利
Center for the column player that leads
领导专栏播放器的中心
to a payoff of four and two for the two
到两个的回报分别为4和2
players okay so in fact given that a
玩家还可以，因此事实上
player if we're looking for Nash
玩家，如果我们正在寻找纳什
equilibrium there things have to be best
平衡那里最好
replies we know that they could never be
我们知道他们永远不会
playing a strictly dominated strategies
发挥严格控制的策略
so we can rule those out they can't
所以我们可以排除那些他们不能
actually be playing you can convince
真的在玩，你可以说服
yourself they can't be playing something
你自己，他们不能玩什么
that's strictly dominated and what's
这是严格控制的，什么是
remaining and so forth so the fact that
剩下的等等，事实是
we ended up with a unique prediction
我们最终做出了独特的预测
here actually tells us that this game
这里实际上告诉我们这个游戏
has a unique Nash equilibrium and the
有一个独特的纳什均衡
only Nash equilibrium is for players to
只有纳什均衡才是让球员
play down in Center so it actually in
在中心播放，所以实际上
this case identifies a unique predicted
这种情况下确定了唯一的预测
play which coincides with the only Nash
与唯一的纳什重合的比赛
equilibrium of this game okay so we've
这个游戏的平衡性好，所以我们已经
got the unique Nash equilibrium DC so
得到了唯一的纳什平衡DC
that that worked very well in that game
在那个游戏中效果很好
let's take a look at another game
让我们来看看另一个游戏
I was slightly change the payoffs of
我稍微改变了
this matrix let's try again in this case
这个矩阵让我们在这种情况下再试一次
you know R is still dominated so in this
你知道R仍然占主导地位
case R always leads to zero for the
情况R总是导致零
column player Center left or Center give
列播放器向左或向中心
higher payoffs so in this case R is
更高的收益，因此在这种情况下R为
dominated by either L or C we can get
由L或C主导，我们可以得到
rid of R and then we can go through
摆脱R然后我们可以通过
again now in this particular situation
现在再次在这种特殊情况下
there's something that's interesting so
有一些有趣的事情，所以
now the column player is indifferent
现在，列播放器变得冷漠
between the two but when we're looking
两者之间，但是当我们在寻找
at the row player we notice that the row
在排播放器中，我们注意到该排
player doesn't have any pure strategy
玩家没有任何纯粹的策略
domination relationships so you know the
统治关系，所以你知道
player gets three here for here compared
玩家在这里得到三个
to zero zero so neither of these
归零归零
strictly dominate the other they get one
严格控制其他人，他们得到一个
always by playing middle so in this case
总是在中间打，所以在这种情况下
they sometimes do better than down if
他们有时候会比失败更好
they're playing middle sometimes do
他们有时在中间打
better than up if they're playing middle
如果他们在中间比赛，那总比起来好
so there's no strict domination when
所以没有严格的统治
we're looking just at pure strategies
我们只看纯策略
but if players are willing to randomize
但是如果玩家愿意随机化
one thing to notice in this game is that
在这个游戏中要注意的一件事是
let's suppose that you played a half on
假设您演奏了一半
up and a half on down
上半下
what would your expected payoff be so if
如果这样，您的预期收益将是多少？
the other player went left and you're
另一个玩家走了，你
playing half up half down you get a path
半上半下玩法
of 1.5 if you were doing this and the
如果您正在执行此操作，则为1.5
other player was playing C you would get
其他玩家在玩C，你会得到
a half of zero and a half of 4 you would
零的一半和4的一半
get two so there's when we look at
得到两个，所以当我们看着
playing a half half then what would we
打一半，那我们会怎么做
end up with if we allow for that mixture
最后，如果我们允许这种混合
right we put in a mixture we would end
正确，我们混合在一起，我们将结束
up having uh oops that happen we would
发生哎呀，我们会
end up with 1.5 1 and a 2 1 so we end up
最终得到1.5 1和2 1所以我们最终
here
这里
with something which strictly dominates
严格控制的东西
middle so playing a half on up and a
中间，所以玩了一半，一个
half on down gives the row player a
一半下来给行玩家一个
strictly higher payoff than they would
严格高于他们的回报
get by playing middle so in this case M
通过打中得到，所以在这种情况下，M
is dominated by the mixed strategy that
由混合策略主导
selects U and D with equal probability
以相等的概率选择U和D
so in that case we can still get rid of
所以在那种情况下我们仍然可以摆脱
M so in that we're down to a reduced
M这样我们就减少了
game now this game doesn't really reduce
现在玩这个游戏并没有真正减少
any further the column players and
任何进一步的专栏选手和
different row player likes up better if
如果不同的行球员喜欢更好
the column player goes left likes down
列播放器走了喜欢下来
better if the com plate goes right so
如果COM板正确，那么更好
what's going to happen in this game now
现在这场比赛将会发生什么
you'd have to take further analysis and
您必须进行进一步分析，
actually if you want to go through and
实际上，如果您想经历
solve the Nash equilibria this game
解决纳什均衡这个游戏
there's a lot of them right so there's
有很多对的所以有
an in fact an infinite number of Nash
实际上是无限数量的纳什
equilibria given that the column player
考虑到专栏选手的均衡
is fully indifferent in this game so you
对这款游戏完全漠不关心，所以您
can go through and analyze all the Nash
可以分析所有纳什
equilibria if you want but the iterative
如果需要均衡，但需要迭代
elimination of strictly dominated
消除严格控制
strategy still gave us a lot of
策略仍然给了我们很多
predictive power in the sense that it it
从某种意义上说，它具有预测能力
collapsed the game down to a much
导致游戏崩溃
simpler game and then it's much easier
更简单的游戏，然后变得容易得多
to analyze what's left okay so iterative
分析还剩下什么可以迭代
removal of strictly dominated strategies
删除严格控制的策略
one nice thing about this is it
一件好事是
preserves Nash equilibria so you can use
保留纳什均衡，因此您可以使用
it if even if you were just wanting to
即使您只是想
to analyze Nash equilibria you can use
分析纳什均衡，您可以使用
as sort of a pre-processing step right
作为预处理步骤的权利
so before you try and compute Nash
所以在您尝试计算Nash之前
equilibria get rid of all the strictly
平衡摆脱了所有严格的要求
dominated strategies and iterate on that
主导策略并对此进行迭代
some games like the first one we looked
一些像我们看过的第一个游戏
at tend to be solvable using this
使用这个可以解决
technique that's called dominant
被称为主导的技术
solvability if it actually collapses to
如果它实际上崩溃到
a single point you were able to solve
您能够解决的一点
that game just by using dominance
该游戏只是通过使用优势
arguments some games won't be but it
争论一些游戏不会，但是
still could be useful to to you to
仍然对您有用
analyze these things what about the
分析这些事情
order of removal so you know we did
删除顺序，所以您知道我们做了
things in a very particular order so
事情以非常特殊的顺序
just noticing that the the column player
只是注意到列播放器
had one
有一个
you know that the right play was was
你知道正确的戏是
strictly dominated and so forth what if
严格控制等等，如果
we started with the with a different
我们从
player or what it would it make a
播放器或它将使
difference if we're dealing with
如果我们要处理的话
strictly dominated strategies then order
严格控制策略然后下令
doesn't matter so no matter how you do
没关系，所以不管你怎么做
this whatever order you do it in you'll
无论您执行什么命令
end up with the same solution you can
最终得到相同的解决方案
spend some time trying to convince
花一些时间试图说服
yourself of that think carefully about
自己仔细考虑
it so that's something you can you'd
这就是你可以做的
have to prove but in fact order does not
必须证明，但实际上顺序并没有
matter in eliminating strictly dominated
消除严格控制的事情
strategies so the logic is very tight in
策略，因此逻辑非常紧密
that respect there's another type of
尊重还有另一种
domination which also makes some
统治也使一些
intuitive sense and people use in games
直觉和人们在游戏中的使用
and that's to weaken the domination
那就是削弱统治
relationship and instead of strict
关系，而不是严格
domination we can consider weakly
统治我们可以弱考虑
dominated strategies what's the idea of
主导策略是什么想法
weakly domination
弱统治
it's very similar to what we had before
这与我们以前的经历非常相似
but instead of having the strict
但是与其严格
inequality hold everywhere right so
不平等现象无处不在，所以
instead of having this hold for all a -
而不是全部保留-
I it just has to hold some sometimes and
我只是有时候要拿着一些
you just need a weakened equality for
你只需要削弱平等
all strategies of the others so the idea
其他人的所有策略，所以这个主意
of a weakly dominated strategy is that
一个弱势控制策略的原因是
it always does a prime always does at
它总是在做素数
least as well as is a and sometime
至少和a和某个时间一样
strictly better so this is still a
严格来说更好，所以这仍然是
strategy you could say okay a prime just
策略，你可以说还可以
you know really it dominates a because
你知道它确实占主导地位，因为
it always does at least as well and
它总是至少也是如此
sometimes that's strictly as well so if
有时也是如此，如果
I'm uncertain at all I might as well go
我完全不确定我是否会去
with the one which always does as well
与总是很好的一个
and sometimes just strictly better so
有时严格来说更好
weakly dominated strategies can be
弱势策略可以是
eliminated as well you can go through
消除以及你可以经历
you can iterate you just go through
你可以迭代你只是经历
games exactly like we did before same
完全像我们之前所做的游戏
kind of thing but one thing that's true
那种事情，但那是真的
about week we dominated strategies is
大约一周我们主导的策略是
that sometimes they could be best
有时他们可能是最好的
replies right so a strategy could be
正确回答，因此可以制定一项策略
a weakly dominated and still turn out to
一个弱势的统治者，仍然导致
be a best reply how could that happen
最好的答复是怎么回事
let's suppose for instance you know we
假设您知道我们
look at a very simple game where the row
看一个很简单的游戏在哪里排
player can go up or down if they go up
玩家可以上升或下降
they get a payoff of one against left
他们得到一个左的回报
and right of the column player and you
和列播放器的右侧，您
know here they get to here they get
知道这里他们到达这里他们得到
three so this would be a situation where
三个所以这是一个情况
down weakly dominates up right you
向下弱主导了你
always get at least as high a payoff and
总是得到至少一样高的回报
sometimes strictly higher but
有时严格更高，但
nonetheless it could be for instance
尽管如此，例如
that if left is the is the strategy's
如果离开的话是该策略的
actually chosen by the column player
由专栏玩家实际选择
then up is still a best reply right so
那么仍然是最好的回复，所以
for instance if we put in payoffs here
例如，如果我们在这里付出
of 1 1 so that the column player is
的1 1这样列播放器是
exactly indifferent between these these
这些之间完全无所谓
two strategies then this is actually a
两种策略，那么这实际上是
Nash equilibrium and so eliminating that
纳什均衡，因此消除了
actually eliminates one of the Nash
实际上消除了纳什之一
equilibria of the game right so
游戏的平衡是这样的
depending on what those payoffs are we
取决于我们的收益是多少
could end up eliminating a Nash
最终可能会消除纳什
equilibrium of the game and you know so
游戏的平衡，你知道
this is a situation where you know we
在这种情况下，您知道我们
end up eliminating something which could
最终消除了可能
be part of an equilibrium what is true
成为均衡的一部分，这是真的
is at least one equilibrium is always
至少总是一个平衡
preserved what's unfortunate is that the
保留的不幸的是
order of removal can matter so which
移除顺序可能很重要
order you remove things in can begin to
为了您删除其中的东西，可以开始
to matter that there are some games
重要的是有一些游戏
which is useful to use in so for
这对于这样有用
instance if you remember the Keynes
如果你还记得凯恩斯的话
beauty contest game that we talked about
我们谈论的选美比赛
earlier where people were naming an
以前人们在命名一个
integer between 0 and 100 think about
考虑0到100之间的整数
trying to solve that via iterative
试图通过迭代来解决
elimination of weakly dominated
消除弱势统治
strategies what what do you end up with
策略您最终会得到什么
so it can still be a useful logic and
因此它仍然是有用的逻辑，
that logic can help you in analyzing
该逻辑可以帮助您进行分析
some games but you do have to
一些游戏，但您必须
it's it's not as tight as strict
不是那么严格
domination because there are situations
统治，因为有情况
where you might want to play a weakly
您可能想在其中玩弱游戏
dominated strategy if you were sure that
如果您确定主导策略
the other player was was going to you
另一个玩家正在找你
know go in a certain direction so for
知道朝某个方向走
instance here if we put in say 2-1 then
实例在这里，如果我们输入2-1然后
uh if we eliminate the column players
呃，如果我们消除专栏选手
dominated strictly dominated strategy
主导严格主导策略
first right so they left weakly
首先向右，所以他们虚弱地离开
dominates right we get rid of of right
支配权利我们摆脱了权利
then what are we left with were left
那我们剩下的是什么
with a situation where the column player
在列播放器的情况下
then sorry the row player is that
那么对不起排球选手
indifferent between the two strategies
两种策略无动于衷
right so if we sort of say okay look
对，所以如果我们说好看
this left dominates right so we get rid
这左边占优势，所以我们摆脱了
of this then we end up with a situation
这样，我们最终遇到了一个情况
where up and left is still left but if
仍然留在上面和左边，但是如果
we removed the role players things first
我们首先删除了角色扮演者的东西
we would remove up first and then we
我们将首先删除，然后我们
would end up with down left so so
最终以左下角结束
depending on on how you go through this
取决于你如何经历
you get different different things that
你会得到不同的东西
are left so there are things that you
被留下，所以有些事情你
know where the order matters and that
知道订单在哪里重要
somewhat problematic okay um iterative
有点问题，好吧，迭代
strict and rationality players maximize
严格合理的球员最大化
their payoffs
他们的收益
they don't play strictly dominated
他们没有严格控制比赛
strategies they don't play strictly
他们没有严格执行的策略
dominated strategies given what remains
考虑到仍然存在的主导策略
we iterate on that Nash equilibria are a
我们迭代得出纳什均衡是一个
subset of what remains so it's a nice
剩下的子集，所以很好
simple solution concept that helps us
简单的解决方案概念对我们有帮助
throw things out of the game and
把东西扔出游戏，
simplify what we're looking at we can
简化我们正在查看的内容
also ask whether or not we see such
还问我们是否看到这样的
behavior in reality do people really act
人们实际上在行动
inconsistent in ways that are consistent
以一致的方式不一致
with eliminating strictly dominated
消除严格控制
strategies and moreover iterating on
策略，并且反复进行
that process
这个过程